Hey, Pop.
Been a while, hasn't it?
Did you see that motorcade roll up?
It's the first time that
the President of the United States
has visited Gaffney.
Can you believe it?
Oh, I wouldn't be here
if I had a choice.
But I have to do these
sort of things now.
Makes me seem more human.
And you have to be a little human
when you're the president.
He couldn't even afford
to pay for his own gravestone.
I paid for it out of my own
scholarship money from The Sentinel.
Nobody showed up
for his funeral except me.
Not even my mother.
But I'll tell you this, though, Pop:
when they bury me,
it won't be in my backyard.
And when they come
to pay their respects,
they'll have to wait in line.
You should let us
take a photo at the grave.
He wants privacy. The man's
honoring his father, for God's sakes.
Synced and corrected by TVfreak83
Here's the info
you were looking for.
And we have that scheduled
for next Tuesday at 10 a.m.
That's still good for you, right?
Excellent. I'll confirm it.
Excuse me.
Yes, sir?
Yes, sir.
The president is ready to see you now.
Jesus.
I'm devastated.
I love this man as if he were my son.
Now, he's a fighter,
and I'm sure that he'll pull through.
Our prayers are with him.
"...said President Underwood
during a press conference yesterday.
The Maryland State Police and
Federal authorities have yet to locate
Mr. Stamper's car or name any suspects."
You want more of this, brother?
Or maybe the sports page?
"Game Six of the World Series
went scoreless for 13 innings
before a rain delay that turned
an already epic evening
into one for the history books."
We need a doctor
in room three-one.
Douglas?
Can you hear me?
I want you to blink if you can hear me.
Again.
My name is Dr. Lanjwani.
The president's office asked me
to look after you personally.
You're getting the very best
of care, okay?
Douglas, I want you to blink
if you can feel this.
Good. Good.
How about this?
Okay. Excellent.
And this?
How about here?
Relax.
Perfectly normal at this early stage.
That's good.
Okay. Get some rest.
Are you gonna hurt me?
I will do whatever you want,
please just don't hurt me.
- Does that hurt?
- A little.
All right, let's go ahead.
Try and make a fist for me.
- Remy.
- What's that?
Remy Danton. Was he here?
He was.
Just checking on your progress.
Go ahead, make that fist for me.
Oh...
- Lion.
- Mm-hm.
Rhinoceros.
- Camel.
- Good.
What color is Rudolph's nose?
- Rudolph?
- Reindeer.
Red.
It's red.
The President of the United States?
Douglas?
Who is the President
of the United States?
Frank Underwood.
- What year are we in?
- 2014.
What month is it?
It's December.
I have to get back to work.
Douglas. Listen to me.
- You suffered a compound fracture--
- I know what I fucking suffered!
I need you to hear me this time.
There was damage
to your left frontal cortex.
Your motor skills will be a struggle.
Your emotions will be unpredictable.
There's a long road ahead,
and we can't rush it.
- Let's do the test later.
- No.
We'll finish it now.
What was your mother's name?
She was young and beautiful.
Jacob fell in love with her
while she was watering a lamb, and...
she became his wife
after he worked seven years
to earn her hand in marriage.
Push back.
Heel into my hand.
Breathe.
Back up. Deep breath.
Ready?
Push. Push.
Hey, Doug.
Focus.
The report I submit to Congress today
includes evidence that would normally
warrant criminal prosecution,
but the Justice Department
won't pursue charges
in accordance
with the presidential pardons.
I'm grateful for the hard work
Ms. Dunbar and her team
have dedicated to their investigation.
In response, I'll be forming
a bipartisan commission to examine
campaign finance reform
so history does not repeat itself,
and so that our nation can heal
from these wounds.
I got bacon-cheese and regular.
Which one you want?
Just a minute.
Remember when you'd never eat a burger
if it didn't have bacon on it?
Dad would get so pissed because he hated
the smell of bacon grease on the grill.
I'm trying to listen, Gary.
The president's hands
are tied. Might as well let him burn.
They're getting their
marshmallows ready.
Look at Underwood's approval rating.
It's worse than Walker's
before he resigned.
That's a deep, deep hole
to climb out of.
The Republicans are gonna
have their fun for a while.
Plenty to hammer him on
in the general. And they're out for blood.
They lost big on education
and entitlement reform.
And if the rumors
about America Works are true...
For the left,
that's just too far to the right
and for the right,
it's too far to the left.
They need me back.
Where? The White House?
We got to turn the corner,
start ramping up for 2016.
He might turn this around.
You don't really think
he's gonna win, do you?
The guy's experienced.
Underwood has a lot...
He'll recover.
He's a behind-the-scenes guy.
He's not comfortable in the spotlight.
- How about you recover first?
- ...glad-handing and kissing babies.
This is gonna be a long 18 months
if this proves any indication.
It can be a lot of chest-thumping
but nothing really getting done.
The Xybenetrin
will help with depression.
The buspirone is for anxiety.
Here you go.
I'd like to prescribe you something
for the pain, but with your...
Well, any patient with a history
of addictive behavior--
I know. It's fine.
I can handle the pain.
He looks a lot better.
No, he's still asleep.
I have to go.
Okay.
Is this a bad time?
No. It's fine.
No, it's just no one told me
you were coming.
Hi. Francis sends his love.
He would visit himself,
but with the media...
No, I understand.
He did come before, when...
- Both of us.
- I know.
I saw the flowers.
Thank you.
- You look well.
- I'm getting there.
I just want to get better
so I can get back to work.
We're looking forward to that.
We can use all the help
we can get, actually.
Yeah. Been watching the news.
Francis, he's at his wit's end.
The Republicans...
won't send him a single bill
he can sign.
- And the Democrats aren't much better.
- Bob Birch?
Blind leading the stupid.
How's Remy working out?
Well, we'd much rather have you there,
but he's doing a fine job.
Doug, do you... recall anything?
- About what happened?
- Why?
Did the police find something?
Not that we're aware of. And we've
asked them to hold off questioning you
until you're feeling more like yourself.
Rachel, she...
I don't remember.
Yes, you do.
A carjacking.
- A man.
- What sort of man?
That part's fuzzy.
It could be anyone, then.
Any man.
Yeah. Any man.
- And he got frightened?
- I chased him and that's all.
- Any idea where she is?
- No.
Because it's important that we find her.
I really don't know.
That's the truth.
I want you to tell all of this
to the police, exactly what you told me,
about the carjacking and the man.
Nothing about her.
I got it.
If you need anything,
or remember anything...
- It's good to see you.
- You, too.
That's good. One more time.
Up and forward. That's good.
Excellent. Breathe.
Good.
Good. Good.
Okay.
Let's try this one.
You're doing a great job.
Keep breathing. Good.
Good job, Doug.
Okay. Moving forward.
You got it.
Great. Great job.
Keep going.
Good. Breathe.
Excellent. Good.
One more.
Great job.
One more time.
It's almost done. Ready?
Keep breathing.
Just his voice.
He said, "Get out of the car."
Anything you can say about the voice?
Was it, uh...
Accent? Lisp? High? Low?
Deep.
That's all I remember.
Then I laid on the horn. I...
I remember him running.
Like a blur, I got out.
I chased him.
I'm not sure. I must have...
What were you doing
in that part of Maryland?
Mr. Stamper?
Sir. What were you doing
in that part of Maryland?
I drive sometimes to think.
There was a lot on my mind with work.
I drive to clear my head.
Have you found the car?
We don't have anything
other than what you just told us.
How's your mood been?
Any episodes?
No. The meds are working.
You just telling me what I want to hear?
No. I feel good.
Okay.
I'm gonna sign your release today.
But it's important
you take it easy at first.
Everything's gonna be
much harder in general.
I know.
Do you have someone
who can look after you?
Yeah. My brother Gary's in from Ohio.
Good. How long is he here for?
- A while, I guess.
- Okay, great.
It's important you go to your meetings.
Stay on top of your sobriety.
Take this.
It's for the steroids I prescribed you.
It's one shot into the right thigh,
once a week. The nurse, she...
- She showed me how.
- Okay.
You do this?
No, it wasn't me.
I talked to my boss.
I can stick around
for another couple of weeks
- while you transition back.
- You should get back to your family.
Nah... Sarah's fine with it.
The kids are, too.
Gary, we've hardly spoken in ten years.
You've already gone above and beyond.
All right.
You want me to go?
I'm fine.
Thanks for everything.
Okay.
I mean, I'm just a phone call
and a plane ticket away.
Safe travels.
Uh...
Take care.
Hey, Gary, I...
Send me some pictures of the kids.
Yeah, I will.
But one of the things I admire
about you is that in Washington, DC,
which is so gridlocked,
you get things done.
And I understand you've got, um,
a new piece of legislation,
a major new initiative
you're rolling out. What is it?
That is correct. It's a new jobs program
that we're calling America Works.
Oh. So it's a fantasy novel.
This is
a fundamentally different look
at how to solve
the problem of unemployment.
It has the size
and the scope of the New Deal.
Oh. So it's a socialist
redistribution of wealth
wherein the baby boomers
will latch onto the millennials
like a lamprey and just keep sucking
until they're as dry as a crouton?
This is about
putting people to work
and avoiding the entitlements entirely.
Well, I like the sound of that.
So what, we're gonna
privatize Social Security
and then raise revenue
by hunting the elderly for sport?
- Good plan. Use that.
- No, as I said,
this is a fundamentally
different approach entirely.
And you think that the Republicans
in Congress will cooperate with you?
Oh, I think that it has been proved
that both parties want the same thing.
A new president in 2016?
No. No, I think actually,
I think unemployment, eradicating it,
and I think a strong economy
is something both parties want.
Okay, speaking of everyone,
there's a recent poll by Reuters.
I wanna get this right.
It says that eight out of ten Americans
agree that you lack, quote,
"effectiveness and leadership."
Uh, look,
I don't let polls like that bother me.
I think that once the nation
sees AmWorks in action,
- they will change their attitudes.
- I'm sorry, "AmWorks?"
I'm sorry-- I didn't realize
it was called AmWorks.
Is that like Amway?
Is it a pyramid scheme?
Is that what you're selling
the American people?
No, it's actually just an abbreviation
to make it easier to say.
Well, if you make it small enough,
uh, maybe it'll be easier to swallow.
You know, even though
you're a Democrat, I respect you.
But let's just take a look
at the facts here for a second.
You've been president for six months,
and again, I wanna get this right,
unemployment has gone up, our trade
deficit with China has increased,
the number of vetoes has skyrocketed.
I'm not entirely sure that I'm confident
that you'll be able to eradicate
unemployment the same way
you've been able
to eradicate your approval polls.
What, you know, what do you--
How are you going to get it across
to the American people?
- Doug?
- Seth?
Yeah, it's me.
Mrs. Underwood,
she gave me this phone, but--
I know. Is something wrong?
No. I want to speak to the president.
Is it urgent?
I want to talk to him
about the America Works program.
- So nothing urgent.
- It's not an emergency, no.
'Cause that's what this phone is for.
Will you pass on my message?
Ah!
Hey.
You're late.
I switched cabs three times.
- Were you being followed?
- Didn't want to take chances.
- You know why I asked you here.
- I don't know where she is.
- Then you need to find out.
- I ran her social, her name,
police records, taxes, everything.
She could be tossed in a ditch
by a john for all I know.
- You work at the FBI.
- What do I get in return?
My protection, like you asked.
I thought you had something to offer.
Something real.
Like money?
Like getting me out of the Bureau. You
make that happen, maybe I can help you.
That was a condition,
for your charges being dropped.
See, you don't still know people.
- I shouldn't have even come here.
- I am your only safety net.
You think I would have turned over
all the AT&T records
without leaving a backup with somebody?
I'm not gonna blow my get-out-of-jail
card on a wild goose chase.
Does anyone suspect anything?
At the Bureau?
Nobody has a clue about her.
If that gives you any peace of mind.
Doug?
Tell him it's urgent.
We're aiming for sometime in May.
As soon as we agree on a date
with the Russian delegation,
you will be the first to know. Uh, Greg.
The Summit with Petrov
here in Washington,
what'll be the focus of the talks?
A bilateral approach to the Middle East.
As you know, the Palestinians
have refused to negotiate
until Israeli troops
leave the Jordan Valley.
We hope to address
this with President Petrov
so that we can move on
to a whole host of other issues.
Sara.
So this bilateral approach doesn't
include Israel and Palestine.
The State Department
is briefing all interested parties.
The summit's really just a first step.
Ayla.
I'd like to change course
to the America Works program.
Please.
I've spoken to a number
of the president's policy advisors,
who say there's been a lot
of disagreement on the economic team
as to exactly what form
this jobs package should take.
- Which advisors?
- Nice try.
To be clear, this is far more
than just a jobs package.
It is a comprehensive plan, which aims
at full employment within two years.
So as such, there are a lot
of details to be worked out.
So your sources are inaccurate.
It's not so much a disagreement
as it is debating the finer points
of the plan. Jess.
Just to follow up.
What are some of the finer points?
Or the broad strokes, even. No one
from the White House has said anything.
When we have a plan to present,
we will present it.
Jess?
Is America Works a reaction
to the president's low approval ratings?
An effort to offer some sign of progress
ramping up to the elections?
We've been working on this plan
since day one.
It has nothing to do
with the approval ratings.
But as for the election...
uh, whose turn is it to ask today?
- Mark?
- Is the president running in 2016?
Today, the priority
is good government, but...
Ask me again tomorrow.
Thank you, everyone.
We've got a window at ten.
I'll call him now.
Please, sit down.
John. Samantha.
You spoke to a journalist
about disagreements in this room?
If that happens again,
you're off the team.
And speaking of the disagreements
in this room,
we now have an even bigger one,
because Remy has shown me
your work so far and...
it's toothless.
I stood in this room three months ago
and gave you all very clear direction.
Social Security, Medicare, Medicaid,
every entitlement program
that is sucking us dry,
I want it all on the table.
And this doesn't go nearly far enough.
So we obviously have
to get back to some basics.
Remind ourselves of some of the facts
that are before us--
- Sir, if I may--
- No, no, no, no.
I will speak first,
and then you will speak, Paul.
This is what
the average senior citizen gets,
one year from entitlements,
whether they were a janitor
or they ran a hedge fund.
That-- This money is a job
we could be giving to a single mother
or a student just out of school.
Now, at the moment,
44 cents of every tax dollar
goes to pay for these programs.
By 2030, it'll be over half, 62 cents.
Entitlements are bankrupting us.
Now, I had Remy conduct a little poll.
"Doing what's best for my country
means doing some things
that I don't like."
Seventy-four percent agreed
with this statement.
Seventy-four percent.
Now, what does that tell us?
We have to do the things
that people won't like.
And even when we do, three out of four
of them will go along with us.
And why?
Because we're promising jobs.
And again, where are the three areas
that we're gonna be
creating these jobs from?
Infrastructure at the state
and federal level.
Increasing the size of the military,
and working with our friends
in the private sector to start--
I'm sorry, sir,
but I have to interrupt.
The programs that you want
to scale back or dismantle
are the bedrock
of the American dream.
You work hard, you pay your taxes--
No, I'm sorry, they were
the bedrock of the American dream.
But they're not anymore.
Certainly not for the ten million people
who are out of work.
But practically speaking,
a thousand special interests,
organized labor,
opposition in both parties.
Now, we can do a version
of what you're proposing--
I don't want a version.
I want a vision.
As head of this team,
and I think I speak for everyone,
- we have done--
- Speaking as the president,
who chose this team
and for whom it works,
I want five hundred billion dollars
to put ten million people to work.
I don't care how much it hurts.
I don't care how controversial it is.
Your job is to find a way.
It's my job to convince Congress
and the American people.
Your job is not to sell me
on your version of my program.
Now, are we all clear
on what our jobs are?
Good, because I want to present this
proposal to leadership in 30 days.
- Let's make it happen.
- Paul?
- Your services are no longer needed.
- Excuse me?
Let's keep it quiet,
let's keep it cordial.
- Thanks for all your work.
- I'll get my things.
I'll have them sent down
to you in the lobby.
Hello?
Yeah. I'm on my way.
Ah! Oh!
Ah! God!
Ah!
Oh!
Mm...
Ahh!
God!
It'll be a few minutes.
Please, have a seat.
- How long have you known?
- Two months.
It hasn't impaired my judgment
on the bench.
And it's early on. We don't expect
any real symptoms for quite some time.
I won't be wandering around the Supreme
Court in my boxer shorts anytime soon.
But I'd like to retire now,
long before we get there.
Well, Justice, I want to thank you
for having the courage
to come and share this news with me.
Are you sure the diagnosis is correct?
My doctor's the same
that treated the vice president's wife.
He's the foremost
Alzheimer's specialist in America.
Yes, I made Donald my vice president.
I'd rather him be a pain in my ass here
than over in Congress.
And even the Republicans couldn't
refuse a man who just buried his wife.
Terrible how quickly Marjory went.
I'm telling you this now so you
have time to think about candidates
before I announce my retirement.
- How much time can you give me?
- How much do you need?
I'm about to introduce
America Works to Congress.
It's sure to be an uphill battle.
And I'd prefer not to add
a Supreme Court nomination to the mix.
The Republicans will just
use it as leverage.
I've heard rumblings.
Entitlements on the chopping block?
All the more reason
to keep you on the bench.
It's sure to be challenged
in the Judiciary.
Mr. President,
I want to spend as much time
with my wife as possible
in the good years that I have left.
When Marjory was ill,
she wanted the same thing.
She left the Smithsonian,
and you know what?
She hated every second of being at home,
of not being productive,
of not doing what she loved.
It made her time
with us much harder, and...
it made her deeply unhappy.
Work is the best distraction.
I wish she hadn't retired.
And, uh...
before she lost her lucid thought,
she said she regretted it, too.
Can you give me six months?
A year at the most? That's all.
Just enough time
to get this program up and running
before I have
to face a Supreme Court fight.
- I need to think it over.
- Oh, of course.
- Speak to your wife.
- I'll walk you out.
- I better get that research center.
- Yes, a deal is a deal.
Now, good God, Donald,
let's get something done.
Now you see why Donald said yes.
He may hate my guts, but there's
nothing like a death in the family
to separate the wheat from the bullshit.
Send him in.
Yes, sir.
The president is ready to see you now.
Doug.
Mr. President.
The doctor told me your recovery
is going very well.
Yeah. Well, there's this.
But everything else is as good as new.
It's great to see you.
Claire and I have been
worried sick about you.
Thank you for the gifts.
- Well...
- For looking out for me.
I don't have that many close friends.
I count you among them.
- I appreciate your saying that, sir.
- Oh, drop the "sir." We're old pals.
Well...
I'm the one who should apologize.
You gave me another chance.
You trusted me.
And what happened,
I take responsibility for that.
- No, for putting you in that position.
- Stop. It's not necessary.
- I endangered you just as--
- Yeah, but all I care about
is that you are alive
and getting better.
Let the rest of it go.
- You know how devoted I am.
- You don't have to say it.
You proved it time and time again.
Now, come on, come on, sit down.
Right here.
I should've taken care of her
when I had the chance.
I haven't found her yet.
But when I do, I'll make sure
that no one else does.
You can count on that, sir.
How is it, uh...?
Probably better
if we don't talk about it.
Right, of course.
Well, they told me you needed to see me.
Well, sir, I...
I know that it's a lot to ask,
and that I probably don't deserve it,
considering the mess I put us in.
And I'm sure you have your doubts.
I realize it couldn't
be anything too visible, but...
I've been following everything
with America Works.
- Oh. Well, that's a ways off.
- But I was thinking that I could help.
There should be a targeted plan
for lobbying committee leadership.
And I can work with the political team,
coordinate with House leg directors,
chiefs of staff--
I was in Gaffney yesterday,
visiting my father's grave.
He never took care of himself.
He ignored his heart problems
and... he paid the price.
You have to respect
your own mortality, Doug.
I don't want to be standing
over your grave.
Now, look...
There is a place
for you here, I promise.
But we have to go about this slowly.
I'll work from home.
Only direct contact with you or Remy.
You know the way
that you can help me the best
is to do exactly
what you're doing right now,
focusing on your recovery.
I would never forgive myself if I
put too much on your plate too soon.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
I'm sorry, I have to go.
But look, I meant what I said.
When you are truly ready.
Yes, sir.
Stay as long as you like.
Three hours ago, we pinpointed him here,
in the Shabwa region of Yemen.
Cooperation?
I spoke to the foreign minister
a few minutes ago.
- Civilians?
- Two dozen, non-IDs.
That's too many.
Our concern is that he could
be on the move at any moment.
Sir, with Petrov
coming to Washington--
It's taken us two years
to track Abdullah down.
We can't ignore every opportunity
between now and the summit.
Do you have eyes on the village?
Yes, sir. He's in this building here.
Kill zone is anyone within 50 meters.
If we take him out with no civilian
casualties, I'll authorize the strike.
Sir, if I may, I really think--
President Petrov is coming
to Washington in less than two months.
Our entire Middle East policy
hinges on that meeting.
We don't want to give
the Muslim community any viable reasons
to obstruct things if we can avoid it.
So find a way to do this
without killing civilians.
Thank you all very much.
May I have a moment?
It's about Claire.
If your husband nominates you,
I can't pull any punches.
Lack of experience. Nepotism.
That's right.
- And you think I'm a dilettante.
- No. But plenty of people will.
I've been preparing
since Francis took office.
What I lack in experience
I'll make up for in work ethic.
Why Ambassador to the UN?
You wield far more influence
as the First Lady.
That's not the same
as contributing in a concrete way.
If we vote down your confirmation,
are you comfortable
with that sort of public embarrassment?
I know that's a risk.
- You're running in 2016, right?
- No comment.
Francis and I are impressed
by how the Republicans
are consolidating around you.
You'll make a good candidate.
Not by linking arms
with the president's wife.
If I'm a disaster,
it makes for a good campaign ad.
If I do a good job,
nobody can fault you.
Either way,
it doesn't hurt your chances in 2016.
Well, I appreciate you
coming by before going public.
It is classy, and thoughtful.
I won't actively block you.
The rest is on your shoulders.
Thank you, Senator.
Tell the president I'm doing this
out of respect to you.
Frank's still on my shit list
till I beat him in the general.
I will.
Why didn't you come right away?
I had a meeting I couldn't miss.
Fucking Washington.
- This is gonna hurt.
- I know.
Ah!
Here's some Percocet.
It'll help with the pain.
I'll write you a 30-day prescription.
I can't.
- I'm not supposed to--
- What was that?
Nothing.
All right. You're good to go.
Hey.
- How did it go with Mendoza?
- Well, I think.
He'll support you?
He won't openly fight it.
Well, that is a big step forward.
- How did it go with Doug?
- No real news.
Hey, are you in here again tonight?
I'm still getting over this cold.
I don't want to get you sick.
Well, don't stay up
with all that too late.
Francis?
When do we announce the nomination?
Listen, I wasn't gonna
bring this up tonight,
but you should know
that there are some serious doubts
from people at the State Department.
You mean Cathy.
And some on her staff.
Like what?
Well, in over your head,
wearing two hats, the obvious things.
And are you saying this
because you don't want to move forward?
Not at all. I'm sharing with you
so you fully understand
- what you're getting into.
- And I do.
Maybe we shouldn't rush this.
- You're having doubts now, too.
- I didn't say that.
Only you should put
more thought into whether
this is the right move for you.
That's all.
Good night, Francis.
Feel better.
Francis.
I want you to announce
the nomination this week.
I don't want to wait.
The timing will never be good.
And I don't want to waste time
when I can be getting
real experience under my belt.
So set a date, hold a press conference,
and let's do it.
Claire!
I was not trying to suggest
that you not be the ambassador
- when I brought up Cathy. I was just--
- We made a deal,
and now you're trying
to back away from it.
- That is not true.
- Then you would've told Cathy
it's happening
to make her peace with that.
- It's not that simple.
- Yes, it is.
- You're the president.
- I can't control Congress.
I'm trying to get two
major initiatives off the ground
and every move I make
will have an effect.
We agreed to this before we ever
stepped foot in this house.
- I know what we agreed to.
- How am I supposed to run for office
at some point if I don't have
a legitimate track record?
We have to survive
the next 18 months,
accomplish something,
and then look ahead.
Francis, let's be realistic.
There's no guarantee you'll get elected.
I need to be prepared if you don't.
You have that much faith in me, do you?
More faith than you have in me,
it seems.
I believe in you
more than anyone, Claire.
Then show it. Nominate me.
I shouldn't have to convince you.
It's not about convincing.
It's about being honest
about the political climate
- that we find ourselves--
- I'm almost 50 years old.
I've been in the passenger seat
for decades.
It's time for me
to get behind the wheel.
That needs to start now.
Before the election.
Because who knows what will happen?
What if you lose?
I will not be
a placeholder president, Claire.
I will win.
And I will leave a legacy.
You mean we will.
Excuse me, sir.
The Secretary of Defense is on the line.
He says it's urgent.
Yes?
Okay.
I'm coming.
Not until I get there.
- I'll be right down.
- Yes, sir.
Get dressed.
I want you to see something.
Come in.
- Here.
- Thank you.
Okay, great.
Get undressed.
How did this happen?
Doesn't matter.
Let me help you.
Sh... I'll... I'll do it.
I'll be gentle.
Don't be gentle.
Like that?
Yeah.
- Oh, whoa! What the fuck?
- It's bourbon.
- I--
- That's all. It's just bourbon.
- Take it.
- I really don't want to.
Nothing's going through the skin.
I just want you to squirt it...
into my mouth.
Okay? Please.
- Is that our target?
- Yes, sir.
Mr. President,
this is a highly classified operation--
I'm clearing the First Lady
for this operation.
Yes, sir. Forgive me, sir.
We are armed and ready, sir.
Abdullah is in one of those
vehicles. We can't tell which one.
If they go in
three different directions,
we wouldn't know where to strike, and
if he makes it back to the mountains,
we'll lose our satellite track on him.
Are those children?
I can't say definitely, sir,
but they could be.
Do we have authorization, sir?
- Proceed.
- Proceed with the launch.
And ten seconds.
And five, four, three...
Target is destroyed, sir.
Thank you, everyone.
I still want it.
All right.
Synced and corrected by TVfreak83