Hey, Pop.
Been a while, hasn't it?
Did you see that motorcade roll up?
It's the first time that
the President of the United States
has visited Gaffney.
Can you believe it?
Oh, I wouldn't be here
if I had a choice.
But I have to do these
sort of things now.
Makes me seem more human.
And you have to be a little human
when you're the president.
He couldn't even afford
to pay for his own gravestone.
I paid for it out of my own
scholarship money from The Sentinel.
Nobody showed up
for his funeral except me.
Not even my mother.
But I'll tell you this, though, Pop:
when they bury me,
it won't be in my backyard.
And when they come
to pay their respects,
they'll have to wait in line.
You should let us
take a photo at the grave.
He wants privacy. The man's
honoring his father, for God's sakes.
Synced and corrected by TVfreak83
Here's the info
you were looking for.
And we have that scheduled
for next Tuesday at 10 a.m.
That's still good for you, right?
Excellent. I'll confirm it.
Excuse me.
Yes, sir?
Yes, sir.
The president is ready to see you now.
Jesus.
I'm devastated.
I love this man as if he were my son.
Now, he's a fighter,
and I'm sure that he'll pull through.
Our prayers are with him.
"...said President Underwood
during a press conference yesterday.
The Maryland State Police and
Federal authorities have yet to locate
Mr. Stamper's car or name any suspects."
You want more of this, brother?
Or maybe the sports page?
"Game Six of the World Series
went scoreless for 13 innings
before a rain delay that turned
an already epic evening
into one for the history books."
We need a doctor
in room three-one.
Douglas?
Can you hear me?
I want you to blink if you can hear me.
Again.
My name is Dr. Lanjwani.
The president's office asked me
to look after you personally.
You're getting the very best
of care, okay?